[Sharp Blade in the Snow]
[نصل حاد في الثلج]
[Episode 10] Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[الحلقة 10] دعم الإدارة. شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
that wretched girl coughed up blood again today.
تلك الفتاة البائسة سعلت دماً مرة أخرى اليوم.
She's extremely weak.
إنها ضعيفة للغاية.
I'm afraid she won't last much longer.
أخشى أنها لن تصمد طويلاً.
But if she still refuses to hand over
لكن إذا استمرت في رفض التسليم
the formula of Phoenix Incense by then,
تركيبة بخور فينيكس بحلول ذلك الوقت،
then we'll...
ثم سنفعل...
Who took it upon themselves
من أخذ على عاتقه؟
to replace the Red Plum with Suoqingqiu rose today?
هل نستبدل وردة البرقوق الأحمر بوردة سوتشينغتشيو اليوم؟
Your Highness, I...
صاحب السمو، أنا...
In Mocheng,
في موتشنغ،
every blade of grass, every flower, every life and every death
كل نصل عشب، كل زهرة، كل حياة وكل موت
is mine to decide—
القرار لي.
including
مشتمل
Feng Li.
فنغ لي.
Understand?
يفهم؟
An important guest has arrived.
وصل ضيف مهم.
Your Highness, you said there was a way to save her.
يا صاحب السمو، لقد قلتَ إن هناك طريقة لإنقاذها.
Please grant me the medicine.
أرجو أن تعطيني الدواء.
Mr. Bai, you have always been proud and untouchable,
السيد باي، لطالما كنت فخوراً ومنيعاً،
yet now you're willing to bow your head for the Queen.
لكنك الآن مستعد للانحناء أمام الملكة.
But you didn't bring the prescription today.
لكنك لم تحضر الوصفة الطبية اليوم.
Let alone an antidote,
ناهيك عن وجود ترياق،
even…
حتى…
Rao Jun.
راو جون.
This medicine
هذا الدواء
can suppress the heart meridian for three days.
يمكن أن يثبط مسار القلب لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
However,
لكن،
where is what I asked for?
أين ما طلبته؟
Mr. Bai, you should know—
سيد باي، يجب أن تعلم—
once you and the Queen are separated by life and death,
بمجرد أن يفصل بينك وبين الملكة الموت والحياة،
there will be no chance to meet again.
لن تكون هناك فرصة للقاء مرة أخرى.
So,
لذا،
a formula in exchange for medicine.
تركيبة مقابل الدواء.
Mr. Bai,
السيد باي،
that's a fair deal.
هذا اتفاق عادل.
After all, I am Li's aunt by birth.
فأنا في النهاية عمة لي بالولادة.
How could I
كيف لي أن أفعل ذلك؟
truly bear to take her life?
هل يتحمل المرء حقاً أن ينهك حياتها؟
She killed her father as a child,
قتلت والدها وهي طفلة،
and now lives in arrogance and indulgence.
ويعيش الآن في غطرسة وانغماس في الملذات.
Countless eyes are waiting for her death.
عيون لا حصر لها تنتظر موتها.
An aunt is a kind of mother as well.
الخالة هي نوع من أنواع الأم أيضاً.
As her mother,
بصفتها والدتها،
I'm protecting her.
أنا أحميها.
Do you understand
هل تفهم
my intentions?
نواياي؟
Thank you, Your Highness.
شكراً لك يا صاحب السمو.
This wine
هذا النبيذ
is called Phoenix Drunk—
يُطلق عليه اسم فينيكس درانك—
the best cure for sorrow.
أفضل علاج للحزن.
Since you love her to the core,
بما أنك تحبها من صميم قلبك،
I'll arrange things for you.
سأرتب الأمور لك.
It's far better than letting her
هذا أفضل بكثير من تركها
keep getting entangled with those slaves.
استمر في التورط مع هؤلاء العبيد.
May you two be bound for life,
أتمنى لكما أن يجمعكما القدر مدى الحياة.
and share intimate moments.
ومشاركة اللحظات الحميمة.
That day, Jiang Zimo said he had found a lead.
في ذلك اليوم، قال جيانغ زيمو إنه وجد خيطاً يقوده إلى القضية.
Now there's been no word at all—
والآن لم يصدر أي خبر على الإطلاق.
something must have gone wrong.
لا بد أن شيئاً ما قد حدث خطأً.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
try these pastries I just made.
جرب هذه المعجنات التي صنعتها للتو.
I added locust flower honey;
أضفت عسل زهور الجراد؛
it's good for the lungs.
إنه مفيد للرئتين.
Bai,
نعم،
have you heard anything about Jiang Zimo?
هل سمعت أي شيء عن جيانغ زيمو؟
What could be more important than your health?
ما الذي يمكن أن يكون أهم من صحتك؟
At least have a few bites first.
تناول بضع لقمات على الأقل أولاً.
Your cooking skills
مهاراتك في الطبخ
are better than the royal chefs.
هم أفضل من طهاة العائلة المالكة.
I'm glad you like it.
يسعدني أنك أعجبتك.
Wait.
انتظر.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
please take care of yourself.
أرجو أن تعتني بنفسك.
One or two sips won't hurt.
رشفة أو اثنتان لن تضر.
This wine is called Phoenix Drunk.
يُطلق على هذا النبيذ اسم "فينيكس درانك".
May you two be bound for life,
أتمنى لكما أن يجمعكما القدر مدى الحياة.
and share intimate moments.
ومشاركة اللحظات الحميمة.
Bai Yu, oh Bai Yu,
باي يو، أوه باي يو،
you're truly despicable.
أنت حقير حقاً.
How could you betray Li's trust?
كيف تجرؤ على خيانة ثقة لي؟
No.
لا.
I mustn't do something so foolish.
لا يجب أن أفعل شيئاً أحمق كهذا.
The doctor has said
قال الطبيب
your condition isn't suited for alcohol.
حالتك الصحية لا تناسب تناول الكحول.
You really shouldn't drink this.
لا يجب عليك شرب هذا.
Why are you being so stingy today?
لماذا أنت بخيلٌ جداً اليوم؟
You won't even spare me a single flask?
لن تمنحني حتى قارورة واحدة؟
I want it—and I'm drinking it.
أريده - وأنا أشربه.
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Bai is from a noble family.
باي ينتمي إلى عائلة نبيلة.
He's never known hardship.
لم يعرف المشقة قط.
He's kind, pure,
إنه طيب القلب، نقيّ،
and utterly sincere to me.
وكان صادقاً تماماً معي.
If I drag him into danger because of me…
إذا جررته إلى الخطر بسببي...
I don't know if that's right or wrong.
لا أعرف إن كان ذلك صحيحاً أم خاطئاً.
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
You dare defy the Princess Royal's orders
تجرؤ على تحدي أوامر الأميرة الملكية
and approach me.
واقترب مني.
Do you have a death wish?
هل لديك رغبة في الموت؟
Your Majesty, you're drunk.
يا صاحب الجلالة، أنت ثمل.
I'm not drunk at all.
أنا لست ثملاً على الإطلاق.
You drink too.
أنت تشرب أيضاً.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
you really have a way of
لديك حقًا طريقة في
keeping me worried sick.
يجعلني هذا الأمر قلقاً للغاية.
Let me get you some water.
دعني أحضر لك بعض الماء.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
It seems you're
يبدو أنك
still drawn to my warmth.
ما زلتُ منجذباً إلى دفئي.
There's a chill
هناك برودة
in the air in Mocheng.
في الهواء في موشينغ.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
you're drunk.
أنت ثمل.
Why are you avoiding me?
لماذا تتجنبني؟
Your Majesty, you seem like
جلالتك، تبدو وكأنك
a different person today.
شخص مختلف اليوم.
Something's wrong.
هناك خطب ما.
This smell...
هذه الرائحة...
There's something wrong with the wine.
هناك خطأ ما في النبيذ.
I know you're all the same kind.
أعلم أنكم جميعاً من نفس النوع.
You want to use me up
تريد استغلالي
and then discard me like a chess piece.
ثم يتخلصون مني كقطعة شطرنج.
I must make the first move.
يجب أن أبادر بالخطوة الأولى.
Are you sure you want to be so cruel?
هل أنت متأكد من رغبتك في أن تكون بهذه القسوة؟
Enough talk,
كفى كلاماً،
you miserable Stone.
يا لك من حجر بائس.
Even you dare to abandon me?
حتى أنت تجرؤ على التخلي عني؟
I'm going to punish you properly.
سأعاقبك كما ينبغي.
You remember me now?
أتتذكرني الآن؟
Feng Li,
فنغ لي,
who am I?
من أنا؟
Stone.
حجر.
Hold me again.
ضمّني إليك مجدداً.
Please don't leave me again.
أرجوك لا تتركني مرة أخرى.
I won't.
أنا لن.
If you wake up
إذا استيقظت
and can still smile at me like this…
وما زال بإمكانه أن يبتسم لي هكذا...
Look at you—a useless heap of flesh.
انظر إليك - كومة لحم عديمة الفائدة.
You're not even worthy to be the lowest blood slave.
أنت لا تستحق حتى أن تكون أدنى عبد من حيث الدم.
I wouldn't even bother to draw your blood.
لن أكلف نفسي عناء سحب دمك.
You'd stain my pool.
ستلطخ مسبحي.
You're nothing but Meng Wu's lackey.
أنت لست سوى تابع لمنغ وو.
You don't deserve to shout here.
أنت لا تستحق أن تصرخ هنا.
You wretch!
يا لك من بائس!
How dare you speak of the Princess Royal's name?
كيف تجرؤ على ذكر اسم الأميرة آن؟
I'll drain you slowly.
سأستنزفك ببطء.
I'll make sure you neither live nor die.
سأضمن ألا تعيش ولا تموت.
And you will watch with your own eyes
وستشاهد ذلك بأم عينيك
as the mistress you serve so faithfully
بصفتك السيدة التي تخدمينها بإخلاص
dies by my hand.
يموت على يدي.
My lord,
سيدي،
only the living can provide warm and nourishing blood.
لا يمكن توفير الدم الدافئ والمغذي إلا من قبل الأحياء .
If you keep beating him like this,
إذا استمريت في ضربه بهذه الطريقة،
he may not survive.
قد لا ينجو.
Silence.
الصمت.
You little fool.
يا لك من أحمق صغير.
You actually tried to steel your courage
لقد حاولت بالفعل أن تقوي عزيمتك
by tricking me into drinking Phoenix Drunk with you.
بخداعي لأشرب معك مشروب فينيكس درانك.
Since you've recognized me,
بما أنك تعرفت عليّ،
I won't hide from you anymore.
لن أختبئ منك بعد الآن.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Last night...
ليلة أمس...
Li,
الذي - التي،
I...
أنا...
How dare you do that to me?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل ذلك بي؟
Shouldn't I be the one
أليس من المفترض أن أكون أنا الشخص المناسب؟
saying that?
هل تقول ذلك؟
Last night, you held me so tightly.
الليلة الماضية، احتضنتني بشدة.
And now you wake up
والآن تستيقظ
and pretend that nothing happened?
ونتظاهر بأن شيئاً لم يحدث؟
Yesterday, you kept...
بالأمس، لقد حافظت على...
Shut up!
اسكت!
If I hadn't been drunk,
لو لم أكن ثملاً،
I would never have mistaken you for someone else.
لم أكن لأخطئ أبداً في اعتبارك شخصاً آخر.
Mistaken me?
هل أخطأت في تقديري؟
You thought I was someone else?
هل ظننت أنني شخص آخر؟
This whole flask
هذه القارورة بأكملها
would never be enough to get me drunk on a normal day.
لن يكون ذلك كافياً أبداً لإسكرني في يوم عادي.
So how did last night turn out like that?
إذن كيف انتهى الأمر الليلة الماضية على هذا النحو؟
So,
لذا،
you mistook me for Stone?
هل ظننتني ستون؟
Shut up!
اسكت!
You're not worthy to speak his name.
أنت لست جديراً بنطق اسمه.
So last night really was nothing but a dream.
إذن، الليلة الماضية لم تكن سوى حلم.
Yun Zhan,
يون زان,
you deceived the sovereign's heart.
لقد خدعت قلب الملك.
You deserve death!
أنت تستحق الموت!
Last night, we drank this Phoenix Drunk together.
شربنا معاً مشروب "فينيكس درانك" الليلة الماضية.
At the height of our closeness,
في ذروة علاقتنا الوثيقة،
you called me by another man's name.
لقد ناديتني باسم رجل آخر.
Was that
هل كان ذلك
your careful test, Your Majesty?
اختباركم الدقيق يا جلالة الملك؟
Were you trying to turn me into his replacement?
هل كنت تحاول تحويلي إلى بديل له؟
Have you said enough?
هل قلت ما يكفي؟
What are you even talking about? That's impossible.
ما الذي تتحدث عنه أصلاً؟ هذا مستحيل.
Your words
كلماتك
truly break my heart.
لقد حطمت قلبي حقاً.
But that man
لكن ذلك الرجل
does deserve to die.
يستحق الموت.
If you truly know nothing of this,
إذا كنت حقاً لا تعلم شيئاً عن هذا،
then perhaps you should think carefully
إذن ربما عليك التفكير ملياً
about who gave you
عن الشخص الذي أعطاك
that wine.
ذلك النبيذ.
Wait.
انتظر.
The doctor has said
قال الطبيب
your condition isn't suited for alcohol.
حالتك الصحية لا تناسب تناول الكحول.
You'd better
من الأفضل لك
not drink this wine.
لا تشرب هذا النبيذ.
I've always been indulgent and reckless.
لطالما كنت متساهلاً ومتهوراً.
You know that.
أنت تعلم ذلك.
I only favored you a little more
لقد فضلتك قليلاً فقط
because you resemble someone from my past.
لأنك تشبه شخصاً من ماضيّ.
Aren't you afraid of me?
ألا تخاف مني؟
Your motives
دوافعك
don't interest me.
لا تثير اهتمامي.
You'll reveal it when you're ready.
ستكشف عنه عندما تكون مستعداً.
What we have is nothing more than an act.
ما لدينا ليس إلا تمثيلاً.
We each take what we need.
كلٌّ منا يأخذ ما يحتاجه.
A word of advice.
نصيحة.
Don't get too caught up in it.
لا تنشغل كثيراً بهذا الأمر.
Did you really not recognize me at all?
هل حقاً لم تتعرف عليّ على الإطلاق؟